Welcome to Sedona Spa.
We're going to be doing an acne treatment today.
We're going to be doing some very deep cleaning on our client, and make sure that we really clear the skin out for her.
So that her skin really starts to come up to more of a normal base.
We're going to start with a little aroma therapy, and start her breathing into the aroma therapy so that she can get used to my hands being on her.
Sarina, take a deep breath. Again. Ok. We've got some steam going, we're going to use our steam. You can hear the noise in the room.
We're going to use our steam along with the softening gel, and the product that's an enzyme, to help open the pores.
We're first going to start with a cleansing treatment.
We're going to do two cleansing treatments, and a deep exfoliation, and then we are going to start again into the process of the softening gel, enzyme, and we're going to steam and open up those pores for a cleaning.
Alright, take a nice, deep breath.
Our steam's just about ready and we'll be turning that off.
And there it is, ready to go.
Alright, take a nice deep breath for me again.